const codingQuestions = [

    // FRONTEND

    {
        id: 1,
        domain: "frontend",
        question: "Center a div using CSS",
        answer: "Use flexbox: display:flex; justify-content:center; align-items:center;",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // REACT

    {
        id: 2,
        domain: "react",
        question: "Create a toggle button",
        answer: "Use useState to toggle true/false.",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // PYTHON

    {
        id: 3,
        domain: "python",
        question: "Check prime number",
        answer: "Loop from 2 to n-1 and check divisibility.",
        difficulty: "medium"
    },

    // JAVA

    {
        id: 4,
        domain: "java",
        question: "Reverse a number",
        answer: "Use while loop and modulo operator.",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // BACKEND

    {
        id: 5,
        domain: "backend",
        question: "Create REST endpoint",
        answer: "Use GET/POST routes to return JSON response.",
        difficulty: "medium"
    },

    // NODE

    {
        id: 6,
        domain: "node",
        question: "Create simple server",
        answer: "Use http module or Express.js.",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // JAVASCRIPT

    {
        id: 7,
        domain: "javascript",
        question: "Find max number in array",
        answer: "Use Math.max(...arr).",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // HTML

    {
        id: 8,
        domain: "html",
        question: "Create form with input and button",
        answer: "<form><input /><button>Submit</button></form>",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // CSS

    {
        id: 9,
        domain: "css",
        question: "Create responsive layout",
        answer: "Use media queries.",
        difficulty: "medium"
    },

    // DATABASE

    {
        id: 10,
        domain: "database",
        question: "Write SQL select query",
        answer: "SELECT * FROM table_name;",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

    // CLOUD

    {
        id: 11,
        domain: "cloud",
        question: "Deploy app to cloud",
        answer: "Use AWS EC2, Vercel, or Netlify.",
        difficulty: "medium"
    },

    // MOBILE

    {
        id: 12,
        domain: "mobile",
        question: "Create simple mobile screen",
        answer: "Use View and Text components in React Native.",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
];

export default codingQuestions;
